<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AssignMate</string>
    <string name="Logdetails">Please fill the details below to continue</string>
    <string name="forgetdetails">Enter your email and we\'ll send you a link to reset your password.</string>
    <string name="signdetails">Please fill the details below to Create your Account</string>
    <string name="log_message">We are Glad to have you back..!!</string>
    <string name="backtolog"> &lt; Back to Login</string>

    <string name="app_description_1">Designed and developed by:\n Pratik Nandvikar \n\nIntroducing AssignMate, your ultimate companion for academic success!  AssignMate is an innovative Android application that revolutionizes the way students handle their assignments and study materials.</string>

    <string name="app_description_2">With AssignMate, students can bid farewell to the stress of tackling complex assignments. Our app offers comprehensive solutions to a wide range of assignments across various subjects, ensuring that students never get stuck or feel overwhelmed.</string>

    <string name="app_description_3">AssignMate goes beyond assignments by providing students with a one-stop platform for all their study needs. You can access a vast repository of well-organized notes, assignments, practicals, and question papers, all in one convenient location.</string>

    <string name="app_description_4">No more rummaging through stacks of papers or endlessly scrolling through disorganized files. With AssignMate, everything is neatly categorized and easily accessible.</string>

    <string name="app_description_5">Our commitment to user experience is evident in every aspect of AssignMate\'s design. We have crafted an intuitive and user-friendly interface that ensures seamless navigation and effortless usage.</string>

    <string name="app_description_6">Whether you\'re a tech-savvy student or just getting started with technology, AssignMate welcomes you with open arms. So, why struggle with assignments and study materials when you can have AssignMate by your side?</string>

    <string name="app_description_7"> AssignMate is here to unleash your academic potential and pave the way for success.</string>

    <string name="Welcome2">Welcome Back..!!</string>
    <string name="msg_token_fmt" > </string>
    <string-array name="subjects">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Programming in Java</item>
        <item>Data Mining &amp; Data Science</item>
        <item>Principles of Operating Systems</item>
        <item>Artificial Intelligence</item>
        <item>Cloud Computing</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="documentType">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Assignments</item>
        <item>Notes</item>
        <item>Practicals</item>
        <item>Question Banks</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>