<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AssignMate</string>
    <string name="Logdetails">Please fill the details below to continue</string>

    <string name="forgetdetails">Enter your email and we\'ll send you a link to reset your password.</string>
    <string name="signdetails">Please fill the details below to Create your Account</string>
    <string name="log_message">We are Glad to have you back..!!</string>
    <string name="backtolog"> &lt; Back to Login</string>

    <string name="app_description_1">Designed and developed by:\n Pratik Nandvikar \n\nIntroducing AssignMate, your ultimate companion for academic success!  AssignMate is an innovative Android application that revolutionizes the way students handle their assignments and study materials.</string>

    <string name="app_description_2">With AssignMate, students can bid farewell to the stress of tackling complex assignments. Our app offers comprehensive solutions to a wide range of assignments across various subjects, ensuring that students never get stuck or feel overwhelmed.</string>

    <string name="app_description_3">AssignMate goes beyond assignments by providing students with a one-stop platform for all their study needs. You can access a vast repository of well-organized notes, assignments, practicals, and question papers, all in one convenient location.</string>

    <string name="app_description_4">No more rummaging through stacks of papers or endlessly scrolling through disorganized files. With AssignMate, everything is neatly categorized and easily accessible.</string>

    <string name="app_description_5">Our commitment to user experience is evident in every aspect of AssignMate\'s design. We have crafted an intuitive and user-friendly interface that ensures seamless navigation and effortless usage.</string>

    <string name="app_description_6">Whether you\'re a tech-savvy student or just getting started with technology, AssignMate welcomes you with open arms. So, why struggle with assignments and study materials when you can have AssignMate by your side?</string>

    <string name="app_description_7"> AssignMate is here to unleash your academic potential and pave the way for success.</string>

    <string name="Welcome2">Welcome Back..!!</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_title">AssignMate App Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_content">
    <![CDATA[
1. Acceptance of Terms: By using the AssignMate, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, please refrain from using the App.\n\n

2. User Responsibilities: You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials and for any activity that occurs under your account. You agree to use the App for lawful purposes and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations.\n\n

3. Intellectual Property: All intellectual property rights, including copyrights, trademarks, and any other proprietary rights related to the App, are the property of AssignMate and its developer. You may not modify, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, software, products, or services obtained from the App.\n\n

4. Privacy Policy: : We want to assure you that the AssignMate does not collect any user personal data. Your privacy is of utmost importance to us, and we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality and security of any information you provide while using the App. Rest assured that there is no collection or use of personal information in any form, and your usage of the App remains completely anonymous. By using the App, you acknowledge and agree that no personal data is being collected or utilized, as we strictly adhere to this privacy commitment.\n\n

5. Content Accuracy: While we strive to provide accurate and reliable information within the App, we do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any content. Users are responsible for verifying the accuracy and appropriateness of the information obtained through the App.\n\n

6. Limitation of Liability: AssignMate and its developers shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages arising out of or in connection with the use or inability to use the App, even if advised of the possibility of such damages.\n\n

7. Modifications and Termination: AssignMate reserves the right to modify or discontinue the App, with or without notice, at any time. We may also revise these Terms and Conditions from time to time. Continued use of the App after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.\n\n

Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using the AssignMate App. By using the App, you signify your agreement to these terms. If you have any questions or concerns regarding these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at assignmate.co@gmail.com
\n\n
\n
Last updated: [24/07/2023]
\n\n
    ]]>
</string>

    <string name="waving">👋Hey, </string>

    <string name="msg_token_fmt"> </string>
    <string-array name="subjects">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Programming in Java</item>
        <item>Data Mining &amp; Data Science</item>
        <item>Principles of Operating Systems</item>
        <item>Artificial Intelligence</item>
        <item>Cloud Computing</item>
        <item>Activities</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="documentType">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Assignments</item>
        <item>Notes</item>
        <item>Practicals</item>
        <item>Question Banks</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>